question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The 2011 movie &quot;The Adventures of Tintin&quot; was directed by Steven Spielberg.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Daft Punk originated in France.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "A Saxophone is a brass instrument.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Stevie Wonder&#039;s real name is Stevland Hardaway Morris.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The alternative rock band, They Might Be Giants, released their album &#039;Flood&#039; in 1990. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Michael Jackson wrote The Simpsons song &quot;Do the Bartman&quot;.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Lead Singer Rivers Cuomo of American rock band Weezer attended Harvard.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle&#039;s &quot;Video Killed the Radio Star&quot; was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Muse is a British (English) rock band", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
